We must inspire the people of Saga to rise up and resist as one!
We can rid this country of the crooks who have taken over everything!
This time, the samurai of Saga will prevail!
Yugiri!
Thanks for the medicine. I'm sorry to trouble you for it.
Has your grandfather's condition improved recently?
There hasn't been much change. He mostly stays in his bed.
Even though I've finally figured out a way for us to reclaim Saga.
You seem to have plenty of comrades on your side now.
Yes, I do. And as a matter of fact, we've all been putting together a petition.
See? Look at it. We're taking this straight to the prefectural magistrate.
We're also going to talk to as many of the elders around here as possible.
I'm sure that'll make a sizable difference.
Right?
How can we accomplish anything with you acting like such a coward?
You're no samurai! Step outside!
It's time someone beat some sense into you!
It sounds like they're getting kind of worked up.
I should go in and intervene.
Excuse me?
How dare you!
I don't care if it's disrespectful. I'm telling you the truth!
I do it. And I'm not even iveling. I love you!